<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title>Brainchild Projects - making</title>
	<subtitle>A Filipino developer&#x27;s projects, thoughts, and experiments</subtitle>
	<link href="https://brainchild-projects.github.io/tags/making/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <link href="https://brainchild-projects.github.io"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2017-09-05T23:01:01+08:00</updated>
	<id>https://brainchild-projects.github.io/tags/making/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Ideas &amp; Execution</title>
		<published>2017-09-05T23:01:01+08:00</published>
		<updated>2017-09-05T23:01:01+08:00</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" href="https://brainchild-projects.github.io/posts/ideas-execution/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://brainchild-projects.github.io/posts/ideas-execution/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ideas are cheap. That’s great. Expend just a few calories and after a while, we
have a lot of them. Executing on them is harder.&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have, well… ideas. Quite a lot of them have been recorded but not a lot have
been built.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have tried building things in the past but none of them were ever completed
or felt finished. I hope to change that and that’s where this site comes in.
With this site, I hope to track my progress in taking some of these ideas to
reality and to also document my thoughts along the way.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site itself is an idea I had years ago that never quite got the time it
needed and most importantly the pragmatism it deserved. I intended it to be
feature-rich like an actual project tracking site. Eventually all that
complexity made it difficult for me to even get started. Because of it, I built
a less than half-baked version out of frustration.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to approach things differently now and hopefully a lot more ideas can
become reality. There are things that I still need to work on like being more
pragmatic or deciding when a project is done. These are skills I hope to learn
along the way with more experience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s to &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.goodreads.com&#x2F;quotes&#x2F;201306-when-you-don-t-create-things-you-become-defined-by-your&quot;&gt;making things
happen&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
